salesloft.com 2016-11-26

# SalesLoft Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

#### (1) What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of information and personal data (“Collected Information”):

(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;

(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of  
our goods or services;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications.

#### (2) Information about website visits

We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views, all of which are also Collected Information.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may send one or more cookies which may be stored by your browser on your computer. The information we obtain from cookies is part of the Collected Information. Our advertisers and service providers may also send you cookies.

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

To improve Our services and this site, We may retain third party service providers to operate this site and help Us monitor, collect and analyze information regarding Your interactions with this website and data you input, including through the use of such providers’ cookies on your computer.

#### (3) Using collected information

Collected Information, including personal data submitted on this website (i.e., data that can be used to identify, contact or locate an individual) will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use all Collected Information, including your personal information to:

(a) administer and improve this website’s usability;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(c) send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;

(d) send to you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology.

(e) for other marketing purposes and to provide other companies with statistical information about our users. Information we provide to other companies will not identify any individual user.

#### (4) Other disclosures

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).

#### (5) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Data transmission over the Internet is inherently insecure and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers.

You are responsible for keeping your passwords confidential. We will not ask you for your passwords.

#### (6) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

#### (7) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites or such site operators’ actions including the collection or use of your personal information.

#### (8) Data Protection

SalesLoft complies with the EU-U.S Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. SalesLoft adheres to the Privacy Shield Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. If you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@salesloft.com. If you are not satisfied with our response, you can contact JAMs here (link: https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield).

#### (9) Do not track

Currently, various browsers – including Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari – offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to Web sites visited by the user about the user’s browser DNT preference setting. SalesLoft does not currently commit to responding to browsers’ DNT signals with respect to the Company’s Web sites, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent. SalesLoft takes privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard.

#### (10) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to privacy (at) salesloft.com or by post to SalesLoft, Inc., 3405 Piedmont Road NE, Suite 250, Atlanta, GA 30305.
